Records of the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia; Law, Appellate, and Criminal Records; Case Papers 1802-1863
Center for Digital Research in the Humanities University of Nebraska–Lincoln
Records of the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia.; Law, Appellate, and Criminal Records; Case Papers 1802-1863
U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia.
976 boxes 450.19 linear feet
RG0021 Entry 6
Restrictions:
Unknown
Scope and Content:
The records are in boxes with labels that provide the year of the case, a term designated by month, the kind of case, and the associated docket number if available.
Subjects:
U.S. District Court;; District of Columbia
Container List:
- Miscellaneous, 1801-1808 (Box 1)
- June-Dec., Civil Appearances, 1808 (Box 2)
- June, Civil Appearances, 1809 (Box 3)
- June, Civil Trials, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Petitions, References and Recognizances, 1809 (Box 4)
- June, Equity, 1809 (Box 5)
- June, Coroner's Inquests, Judicials, 1-82, 1809 (Box 6)
- June, Judicials, 83-166, 1809 (Box 7)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-186, 1809 (Box 8)
- December, Civil Appearances, 187-373, 1809 (Box 9)
- December, Civil Trials, 10-129, 1809 (Box 10)
- December, Civil Trials, 132-245, 1809 (Box 11)
- December, Appeals, Bail Bonds, Criminal Appearances, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, 1809 (Box 12)
- December, Equity, 1809 (Box 13)
- December, Judicials, 1809 (Box 14)
- December, References, 1-65, 1809 (Box 15)
- December, References, 66-129, 1809 (Box 16)
- June, Civil Appearances, 2-131, 1810 (Box 17)
- June, Civil Appearances, 132-339, 1810 (Box 18)
- June, Civil Trials, 15-122, 1810 (Box 19)
- June, Civil Trials, 124-221, 1810 (Box 20)
- June, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials and Administration Bonds, 1810 (Box 21)
- June, Imparlances, Appeals, Recognizances and Coroner's Inquests, 1810 (Box 22)
- June, Judicials, 1810 (Box 23)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-194, 1810 (Box 24)
- December, Civil Appearances, 200-498, 1810 (Box 25)
- December, Civil Trials, 6-104, 1810 (Box 26)
- December, Civil Trials, 106-210, 1810 (Box 27)
- December, Civil Trials, 212-231, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials and Imparlances, 1810 (Box 28)
- December, Judicials, 1810 (Box 29)
- December, Appeals, Presentments, Recognizances and Rough Bundle, 1810 (Box 30)
- June, Civil Appearances, 1-175, 1811 (Box 31)
- June, Civil Appearances, 177-427, 1811 (Box 32)
- June, Civil Trials, 3-177, 1811 (Box 33)
- June, Civil Trials, 190-201, Criminal Appearances, Recognizances and Rough Bundle, 1811 (Box 34)
- June, Imparlances, 1811 (Box 35)
- June, Judicials, 1811 (Box 36)
- December, Civil Appearances, 3-127, 1811 (Box 37)
- December, Civil Trials, 4-120, 1811 (Box 38)
- December, Civil Trials, 123-218, 1811 (Box 39)
- December, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances and Rough Bundle, 1811 (Box 40)
- December, Imparlances, 1811 (Box 41)
- December, Judicials, 1811 (Box 42)
- June, Civil Appearances, 1-161, 1812 (Box 43)
- June, Civil Appearances, 163-375, 1812 (Box 44)
- June, Civil Trials, 1-105, 1812 (Box 45)
- June, Civil Trials, 107-197, 1812 (Box 46)
- June, Civil Trials, 199-263, 1812 (Box 47)
- June, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances and Rough Bundle, 1812 (Box 48)
- June, Imparlances, 1812 (Box 49)
- June, Judicials, 1812 (Box 50)
- December, Civil Trials, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials and Rough Bundle, 1812 (Box 51)
- June, Civil Appearances, 1-162, 1813 (Box 52)
- June, Civil Appearances, 167-371, 1813 (Box 53)
- June, Civil Trials, 4-218, 1813 (Box 54)
- June, Civil Trials, 220-261, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Appeals and Rough Bundle, 1813 (Box 55)
- June, Imparlances and Recognizances, Judicials, 1-35, 1813 (Box 56)
- June, Judicials, 37-185, 1813 (Box 57)
- December, Civil Appearances, 4-154, 1813 (Box 58)
- December, Civil Appearances, 156-375, 1813 (Box 59)
- December, Civil Trials, 6-114, 1813 (Box 60)
- December, Civil Trials, 116-197, 1813 (Box 61)
- December, Civil Trials, 199-293, 1813 (Box 62)
- December, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, Recognizances and Rough Bundle, 1813 (Box 63)
- December, Judicials, 1-72, 1813 (Box 64)
- December, Judicials, 74-141, 1813 (Box 65)
- June, Civil Appearances, 2-169, 1814 (Box 66)
- June, Civil Appearances, 173-385, 1814 (Box 67)
- June, Civil Trials, 10-126, 1814 (Box 68)
- June, Civil Trials, 128-216, 1814 (Box 69)
- June, Appeals, Criminal Appeals, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-50, 1814 (Box 70)
- June, Judicials, 51-144, 1814 (Box 71)
- June, Judicials, 146-203, 1814 (Box 72)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-165, 1814 (Box 73)
- December, Civil Appearances, 176-404, 1814 (Box 74)
- December, Civil Trials, 5-160, 1814 (Box 75)
- December, Civil Trials, 162-247, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1814 (Box 76)
- December, Imparlances, Judicials, 6-60, 1814 (Box 77)
- December, Judicials, 61-124, Appeal Bonds, Rough Bundle, 1814 (Box 78)
- June, Civil Appearances, 2-199, 1815 (Box 79)
- June, Civil Appearances, 201-347, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1815 (Box 80)
- June, Civil Trials, 90-249, 1815 (Box 81)
- June, Civil Trials, 255-285, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-41, 1815 (Box 82)
- June, Judicials, Petitions, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 43-125, 1815 (Box 83)
- December, Civil Appearances, 9-237, 1815 (Box 84)
- December, Civil Appearances, 240-455, Civil Trials, 12-68, 1815 (Box 85)
- December, Civil Trials, 70-176, 1815 (Box 86)
- December, Civil Trials, 180-299, 1815 (Box 87)
- December, Civil Trials, 303-329, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1815 (Box 88)
- December, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-88, 1815 (Box 89)
- December, Judicials, 90-169, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1815 (Box 90)
- June, Civil Appearances, 1-132, 1816 (Box 91)
- June, Civil Appearances, 136-322, 1816 (Box 92)
- June, Civil Appearances, 334-515, 1816 (Box 93)
- June, Civil Trials, 1-139, 1816 (Box 94)
- June, Civil Trials, 144-200, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1816 (Box 95)
- June, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-55, 1816 (Box 96)
- June, Judicials, 57-130, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1816 (Box 97)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-168, 1816 (Box 98)
- December, Civil Appearances, 185-417, 1816 (Box 99)
- December, Civil Appearances, 418-679, 1816 (Box 100)
- December, Civil Trials, 1-160, 1816 (Box 101)
- December, Civil Trials, 162-264, 1816 (Box 102)
- December, Civil Trials, 266-341, Criminal Appearances, 1816 (Box 103)
- December, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, 1816 (Box 104)
- December, Judicials, Appeals, Coroner's Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1816 (Box 105)
- June, Civil Appearances, 1-101, 1817 (Box 106)
- June, Civil Appearances, 103-202, 1817 (Box 107)
- June, Civil Appearances, 204-430, 1817 (Box 108)
- June, Civil Appearances, 431-520, 1817 (Box 109)
- June, Civil Appearances, 521-696, 1817 (Box 110)
- June, Civil Appearances, 698-938, 1817 (Box 111)
- June, Civil Trials, 7-189, 1817 (Box 112)
- June, Civil Trials, 192-297, 1817 (Box 113)
- June, Civil Trials, 301-360, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, Appeal Bonds, 1817 (Box 114)
- June, Judicials, 1-128, 1817 (Box 115)
- June, Judicials, 130-168, Presentments, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1817 (Box 116)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-272, 1817 (Box 117)
- December, Civil Appearances, 274-513, 1817 (Box 118)
- December, Civil Appearances, 517-789, 1817 (Box 119)
- December, Civil Appearances, 791-1008, 1817 (Box 120)
- December, Civil Trials, 6-242, 1817 (Box 121)
- December, Civil Trials, 247-335, 1817 (Box 122)
- December, Civil Trials, 337-446, Appeal Bonds, Coroner's Inquests, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1817 (Box 123)
- December, Imparlances, 3-420, 1817 (Box 124)
- December, Imparlances, 422-567, Judicials, 1-93, 1817 (Box 125)
- December, Judicials, 95-187, 1817 (Box 126)
- June, Civil Appearances, 2-172, 1818 (Box 127)
- June, Civil Appearances, 174-397, 1818 (Box 128)
- June, Civil Appearances, 409-697, 1818 (Box 129)
- June, Civil Appearances, 717-964, Civil Trials, 12-99, 1818 (Box 130)
- June, Civil Trials, 101-239, 1818 (Box 131)
- June, Civil Trials, 241-309, 1818 (Box 132)
- June, Civil Trials, 310-399, 1818 (Box 133)
- June, Civil Trials, 402-475, 1818 (Box 134)
- June, Civil Trials, 476-549, 1818 (Box 135)
- June, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, 1-75, 1818 (Box 136)
- June, Imparlances, 77-559, Appeals, 1818 (Box 137)
- June, Judicials, 1-115, 1818 (Box 138)
- June, Judicials, 117-224, 1818 (Box 139)
- June, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, John Tayloe's checks, 1818 (Box 140)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-185, 1818 (Box 141)
- December, Civil Appearances, 189-471, 1818 (Box 142)
- December, Civil Appearances, 178-663, 1818 (Box 143)
- December, Civil Appearances, 666-971, 1818 (Box 144)
- December, Civil Appearances, 873-1221, 1818 (Box 145)
- December, Civil Trials, 6-193, 1818 (Box 146)
- December, Civil Trials, 195-293, 1818 (Box 147)
- December, Civil Trials, 296-388, 1818 (Box 148)
- December, Civil Trials, 391-494, 1818 (Box 149)
- December, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Appeal Bonds, 1818 (Box 150)
- December, Imparlances, 1818 (Box 151)
- December, Judicials, 2-109, 1818 (Box 152)
- December, Judicials, 111-241, 1818 (Box 153)
- December, Judicials, 243-301, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1818 (Box 154)
- June, Civil Appearances, 3-222, 1819 (Box 155)
- June, Civil Appearances, 224-464, 1819 (Box 156)
- June, Civil Appearances, 478-775, 1819 (Box 157)
- June, Civil Appearances, 778-1310, 1819 (Box 158)
- June, Civil Trials, 21-289, 1819 (Box 159)
- June, Civil Trials, 292-424, 1819 (Box 160)
- June, Civil Trials, 426-589, 1819 (Box 161)
- June, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Criminal Papers, Appeal Bonds, Rough Bundle, 1819 (Box 162)
- June, Imparlances, 1819 (Box 163)
- June, Judicials, 1-102, 1819 (Box 164)
- June, Judicials, 104-241, 1819 (Box 165)
- December, Civil Appearances, 4-195, 1819 (Box 166)
- December, Civil Appearances, 199-312, 1819 (Box 167)
- December, Civil Appearances, 314-512, 1819 (Box 168)
- December, Civil Appearances, 527-795, 1819 (Box 169)
- December, Civil Appearances, 801-1187, 1819 (Box 170)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1191-1506, 1819 (Box 171)
- December, Civil Trials, 17-415, 1819 (Box 172)
- December, Civil Trials, 417-528, 1819 (Box 173)
- December, Civil Trials, 530-649, 1819 (Box 174)
- December, Civil Trials, 651-906, 1819 (Box 175)
- December, Imparlances, 4-322, 1819 (Box 176)
- December, Imparlances, 326-808, 1819 (Box 177)
- December, Judicials, 2-116, 1819 (Box 178)
- December, Judicials, 118-238, 1819 (Box 179)
- December, Judicials, 243-276, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Rough Bundle, 1819 (Box 180)
- June, Civil Appearances, 4-166, 1820 (Box 181)
- June, Civil Appearances, 169-355, 1820 (Box 182)
- June, Civil Appearances, 358-657, 1820 (Box 183)
- June, Civil Appearances, 659-974, 1820 (Box 184)
- June, Civil Appearances, 985-1183, 1820 (Box 185)
- June, Civil Trials, 13-623, 1820 (Box 186)
- June, Civil Trials, 625-707, 1820 (Box 187)
- June, Civil Trials, 710-820, 1820 (Box 188)
- June, Civil Trials, 824-908, 1820 (Box 189)
- June, Civil Trials, 910-1005, 1820 (Box 190)
- June, Civil Trials, 1011-1121, 1820 (Box 191)
- June, Appeal Bonds, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Presentments, Rough Bundle, 1820 (Box 192)
- June, Imparlances, 1-598, 1820 (Box 193)
- June, Imparlances, 604-1045, Judicials, 1-55, 1820 (Box 194)
- June, Judicials, 58-167, 1820 (Box 195)
- June, Judicials, 169-283, 1820 (Box 196)
- December, Criminal Trials, Rough Bundle, 1820 (Box 197)
- April, Civil Appearances, 1-189, 1821 (Box 198)
- April, Civil Appearances, 191-283, 1821 (Box 199)
- April, Civil Appearances, 285-496, 1821 (Box 200)
- April, Civil Appearances, 503-1059, 1821 (Box 201)
- April, Civil Appearances, 1072-1301, 1821 (Box 202)
- April, Civil Appearances, 1305-1623, 1821 (Box 203)
- April, Civil Trials, 4-270, 1821 (Box 204)
- April, Civil Trials, 273-434, 1821 (Box 205)
- April, Civil Trials, 439-547, 1821 (Box 206)
- April, Civil Trials, 550-617, 1821 (Box 207)
- April, Civil Trials, 619-698, 1821 (Box 208)
- April, Civil Trials, 700-782, 1821 (Box 209)
- April, Civil Trials, 784-865, 1821 (Box 210)
- April, Civil Trials, 867-941, 1821 (Box 211)
- April, Civil Trials, 942-1012, 1821 (Box 212)
- April, Civil Trials, 1014-1092, 1821 (Box 213)
- April, Civil Trials, 1094-1187, 1821 (Box 214)
- April, Civil Trials, 1190-1255, Criminal Appearances, 1821 (Box 215)
- April, Criminal Trials, Appeal Bonds, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1821 (Box 216)
- April, Imparlances, 10-304, 1821 (Box 217)
- April, Imparlances, 315-821, 1821 (Box 218)
- April, Judicials, 2-123, 1821 (Box 219)
- April, Judicials, 126-228, 1821 (Box 220)
- April, Judicials, 230-360, 1821 (Box 221)
- April, Judicials, 364-466, 1821 (Box 222)
- April, Judicials, 469-588, 1821 (Box 223)
- October, Civil Appearances, 2-175, 1821 (Box 224)
- October, Civil Appearances, 176-289, 1821 (Box 225)
- October, Civil Appearances, 291-459, 1821 (Box 226)
- October, Civil Appearances, 463-733, 1821 (Box 227)
- October, Civil Appearances, 737-927, 1821 (Box 228)
- October, Civil Trials, 2-273, 1821 (Box 229)
- October, Civil Trials, 275-433, 1821 (Box 230)
- October, Civil Trials, 440-555, 1821 (Box 231)
- October, Civil Trials, 557-649, 1821 (Box 232)
- October, Civil Trials, 651-762, 1821 (Box 233)
- October, Civil Trials, 765-878, 1821 (Box 234)
- October, Civil Trials, 881-998, 1821 (Box 235)
- October, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1821 (Box 236)
- October, Imparlances, 1821 (Box 237)
- October, Judicials, 1-123, 1821 (Box 238)
- October, Judicials, 124-225, 1821 (Box 239)
- October, Judicials, 226-335, 1821 (Box 240)
- October, Judicials, 336-467, 1821 (Box 241)
- October, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1821 (Box 242)
- April, Civil Appearances, 1-129, 1822 (Box 243)
- April, Civil Appearances, 131-250, 1822 (Box 244)
- April, Civil Appearances, 252-467, 1822 (Box 245)
- April, Civil Appearances, 469-743, 1822 (Box 246)
- April, Civil Appearances, 748-993, 1822 (Box 247)
- April, Civil Trials, 9-202, 1822 (Box 248)
- April, Civil Trials, 205-365, 1822 (Box 249)
- April, Civil Trials, 367-508, 1822 (Box 250)
- April, Civil Trials, 564-634, 1822 (Box 251)
- April, Civil Trials, 641-740, 1822 (Box 252)
- April, Civil Trials, 742-837, 1822 (Box 253)
- April, Civil Trials, 840-931, 1822 (Box 254)
- April, Civil Trials, 932-1036, 1822 (Box 255)
- April, Civil Trials, 1039-1162, 1822 (Box 256)
- April, Civil Trials, 1169-1244, 1822 (Box 257)
- April, Civil Trials, 1246-1322, 1822 (Box 258)
- April, Civil Trials, 1325-1432, 1822 (Box 259)
- April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1822 (Box 260)
- April, Imparlances, Recognizances, Rough bundle, 1822 (Box 261)
- April, Judicials, 1-114, 1822 (Box 262)
- April, Judicials, 115-225, 1822 (Box 263)
- April, Judicials, 227-341, 1822 (Box 264)
- April, Judicials, 378-540, 1822 (Box 265)
- April, Titlings for Writs, Titlings for Executions, 1822 (Box 266)
- October, Civil Appearances, 3-132, 1822 (Box 267)
- October, Civil Appearances, 133-229, 1822 (Box 268)
- October, Civil Appearances, 231-329, 1822 (Box 269)
- October, Civil Appearances, 344-520, 1822 (Box 270)
- October, Civil Trials, 8-297, 1822 (Box 271)
- October, Civil Trials, 301-590, 1822 (Box 272)
- October, Civil Trials, 592-702, 1822 (Box 273)
- October, Civil Trials, 706-848, 1822 (Box 274)
- October, Civil Trials, 850-966, 1822 (Box 275)
- October, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1822 (Box 276)
- October, Imparlances, Recognizances, 1822 (Box 277)
- October, Judicials, 1-157, 1822 (Box 278)
- October, Judicials, 159-331, 1822 (Box 279)
- October, Judicials, 343-544, Rough Bundle, 1822 (Box 280)
- April, Civil Appearances, 3-164, 1823 (Box 281)
- April, Civil Appearances, 165-279, 1823 (Box 282)
- April, Civil Appearances, 281-480, 1823 (Box 283)
- April, Civil Appearances, 483-833, 1823 (Box 284)
- April, Civil Appearances, 835-1093, 1823 (Box 285)
- April, Civil Trials, 3-307, 1823 (Box 286)
- April, Civil Trials, 309-566, 1823 (Box 287)
- April, Civil Trials, 570-702, 1823 (Box 288)
- April, Civil Trials, 710-835, 1823 (Box 289)
- April, Civil Trials, 837-951, 1823 (Box 290)
- April, Civil Trials, 954-1339, 1823 (Box 291)
- April, Criminal Appearances, 1823 (Box 292)
- April, Appeals, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1823 (Box 293)
- April, Imparlances, Recognizances, 1823 (Box 294)
- April, Judicials, 2-130, 1823 (Box 295)
- April, Judicials, 131-278, 1823 (Box 296)
- April, Judicials, 330-478, 1823 (Box 297)
- October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, 1823 (Box 298)
- October, Civil Appearances, 146-274, 1823 (Box 299)
- October, Civil Appearances, 276-515, 1823 (Box 300)
- October, Civil Appearances, 518-852, 1823 (Box 301)
- October, Civil Trials, 1-353, 1823 (Box 302)
- October, Civil Trials, 356-457, 1823 (Box 303)
- October, Civil Trials, 460-604, 1823 (Box 304)
- October, Civil Trials, 606-678, 1823 (Box 305)
- October, Civil Trials, 680-770, 1823 (Box 306)
- October, Civil Trials, 771-849, 1823 (Box 307)
- October, Civil Trials, 853-980, 1823 (Box 308)
- October, Civil Trials, 983-1076, 1823 (Box 309)
- October, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1823 (Box 310)
- October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1823 (Box 311)
- October, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-59, 1823 (Box 312)
- October, Judicials, 60-178, 1823 (Box 313)
- October, Judicials, 180-322, 1823 (Box 314)
- April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, 1824 (Box 315)
- April, Civil Appearances, 162-391, 1824 (Box 316)
- April, Civil Appearances, 408-740, 1824 (Box 317)
- April, Civil Trials, 1-312, 1824 (Box 318)
- April, Civil Trials, 329-489, 1824 (Box 319)
- April, Civil Trials, 495-645, 1824 (Box 320)
- April, Civil Trials, 647-726, 1824 (Box 321)
- April, Civil Trials, 729-815, 1824 (Box 322)
- April, Civil Trials, 819-909, 1824 (Box 323)
- April, Civil Appearances, 911-1005, 1824 (Box 324)
- April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1824 (Box 325)
- April, Imparlances, Judicials, 4-97, 1824 (Box 326)
- April, Judicials, 99-297, 1824 (Box 327)
- April, Judicials, 319-504, 1824 (Box 328)
- December, Civil Appearances, 2-165, 1824 (Box 329)
- December, Civil Appearances, 167-365, 1824 (Box 330)
- December, Civil Appearances, 374-763, 1824 (Box 331)
- December, Civil Trials, 1-100, 1824 (Box 332)
- December, Civil Trials, 102-274, 1824 (Box 333)
- December, Civil Trials, 276-460, 1824 (Box 334)
- December, Civil Trials, 465-620, 1824 (Box 335)
- December, Civil Trials, 625-760, 1824 (Box 336)
- December, Civil Trials, 763-880, 1824 (Box 337)
- December, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1824 (Box 338)
- December, Imparlances, 1824 (Box 339)
- December, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1824 (Box 340)
- December, Judicials, 3-140, 1824 (Box 341)
- December, Judicials, 141-232, 1824 (Box 342)
- December, Judicials, 233-502, 1824 (Box 343)
- May, Civil Appearances, 2-155, 1825 (Box 344)
- May, Civil Appearances, 160-370, 1825 (Box 345)
- May, Civil Appearances, 379-485, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1825 (Box 346)
- May, Civil Trials, 3-250, 1825 (Box 347)
- May, Civil Trials, 254-414, 1825 (Box 348)
- May, Civil Trials, 416-516, 1825 (Box 349)
- May, Civil Trials, 518-617, 1825 (Box 350)
- May, Civil Trials, 619-705, Appeals, Recognizances, 1825 (Box 351)
- May, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, 1825 (Box 352)
- May, Judicials, 1-275, 1825 (Box 353)
- May, Judicials, 277-452, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1825 (Box 354)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-171, 1825 (Box 355)
- December, Civil Appearances, 175-517, 1825 (Box 356)
- December, Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, 1825 (Box 357)
- December, Civil Trials, 1-170, 1825 (Box 358)
- December, Civil Trials, 175-379, 1825 (Box 359)
- December, Civil Trials, 381-466, 1825 (Box 360)
- December, Civil Trials, 470-575, 1825 (Box 361)
- December, Civil Trials, 577-684, 1825 (Box 362)
- December, Civil Trials, 1-138, 1825 (Box 363)
- December, Civil Trials, 172-335, 1825 (Box 364)
- December, Civil Trials, 337-447, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1825 (Box 365)
- May, Civil Appearances, 1-150, 1826 (Box 366)
- May, Civil Appearances, 153-412, 1826 (Box 367)
- May, Civil Trials, 1-198, 1826 (Box 368)
- May, Civil Trials, 200-350, 1826 (Box 369)
- May, Civil Trials, 354-437, 1826 (Box 370)
- May, Civil Trials, 440-511, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1826 (Box 371)
- May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, 1826 (Box 372)
- May, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-54, 1826 (Box 373)
- May, Judicials, 212-422, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1826 (Box 374)
- December, Civil Appearances, 6-155, 1826 (Box 375)
- December, Civil Appearances, 157-375, 1826 (Box 376)
- December, Civil Appearances, 378-638, 1826 (Box 377)
- December, Civil Trials, 2-225, 1826 (Box 378)
- December, Civil Trials, 231-364, 1826 (Box 379)
- December, Civil Trials, 367-458, 1826 (Box 380)
- December, Civil Trials, 465-575, 1826 (Box 381)
- December, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1826 (Box 382)
- December, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-239, 1826 (Box 383)
- December, Judicials, 241-367, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1826 (Box 384)
- May, Civil Appearances, 8-239, 1827 (Box 385)
- May, Civil Appearances, 242-458, Criminal Appearances, 1827 (Box 386)
- May, Civil Trials, 23-222, 1827 (Box 387)
- May, Civil Trials, 224-341, 1827 (Box 388)
- May, Civil Trials, 344-443, 1827 (Box 389)
- May, Judicials, 4-212, 1827 (Box 390)
- May, Judicials, 214-369, 1827 (Box 391)
- May, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1827 (Box 392)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-204, 1827 (Box 393)
- December, Civil Appearances, 208-438, Criminal Appearances, 1827 (Box 394)
- December, Civil Trial, 9-212, 1827 (Box 395)
- December, Civil Trials, 251-370, 1827 (Box 396)
- December, Civil Trials, 372-521, 1827 (Box 397)
- December, Appeals, Imparlances, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1827 (Box 398)
- December, Judicials, 1-189, 1827 (Box 399)
- December, Judicials, 191-296, 1827 (Box 400)
- May, Civil Appearances, 2-353, 1828 (Box 401)
- May, Civil Appearances, 367-432, Criminal Appearances, 1828 (Box 402)
- May, Civil Trials, 1-172, 1828 (Box 403)
- May, Civil Trials, 174-328, 1828 (Box 404)
- May, Civil Trials, 330-437, 1828 (Box 405)
- May, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1828 (Box 406)
- May, Judicials, 1-169, 1828 (Box 407)
- May, Judicials, 172-244, 1828 (Box 408)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-246, 1828 (Box 409)
- December, Civil Appearances, 257-452, Criminal Appearances, 1828 (Box 410)
- December, Civil Trials, 5-176, 1828 (Box 411)
- December, Civil Trials, 179-277, 1828 (Box 412)
- December, Civil Trials, 281-369, 1828 (Box 413)
- December, Civil Trials, 370-440, Appeals, 1828 (Box 414)
- December, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1828 (Box 415)
- December, Judicials, 1-140, 1828 (Box 416)
- December, Judicials, 157-232, 1828 (Box 417)
- May, Civil Appearances, 1-275, 1829 (Box 418)
- May, Civil Appearances, 284-396, Imparlances, 1829 (Box 419)
- May, Criminal Appearances, 1829 (Box 420)
- May, Civil Trials, 15-225, 1829 (Box 421)
- May, Civil Trials, 227-337, 1829 (Box 422)
- May, Civil Trials, 338-444, 1829 (Box 423)
- May, Judicials, 1-182, 1829 (Box 424)
- Judicials, 184-221, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1829 (Box 425)